本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
翻译：装汁的容器    Soomii    红豆包    Iz
校对：Ｊ小糯      时间轴：grace
■
后期：鱼骨头      总监：stephanie
《开心汉堡店》
第一季第六集
鲍勃
Bob!
鲍勃  你脸上有东西
Bob! Hey, I think you missed a spot!
没事了  原来是你的胡子
Oh, never mind. That's just your mustache!
中招了吧
Ka-boom!
吉米  这招不错
Ha-ha. Ha-ha, Jimmy! Good one.
但至少我能长出胡子  你就不能
Uh, at least I could grow one. You can't!
吉恩  露易丝  帮我想个好段子
Gene? Louise? How about a "ka-boom"?
你可以想出一个更好的  老爸
You can do better than that, dad.
没错  我看好你哦
Yeah, step it up.
这方面还是你们比较擅长  快帮我想想
Okay, you do better. Give me something.
这个嘛  让我想想
How about, I don't know...
鞋不错嘛  吉米  这鞋是男人穿的吗
Nice shoes, Jimmy. Do they make them for men, too? Ha!
这个  挺好  我说  吉...
That's, uh... that's good. Hey, Ji...
他们走了
Oh. They're gone.
靠  我讨厌吉米・派丝多
God, I hate Jimmy Pesto
我讨厌他们店恶心的食物
with his crappy food
和...  络绎不绝的客人
and all his... customers.
先别想你那蠢对手了
Oh, forget about your silly rivalry for one minute.
鲍勃  听我说
Bob, listen, come here.
蒂娜的生日快到了
Tina's birthday's coming up,
我觉得我们应该准备点特别的东西
and I think we should do something special
因为她就要13岁了
since she's turning 13.
过完这个生日她就要成为女人了
This is the year she becomes a woman.
我不想听这一套
Yeah, I don't want to hear this.
鲍勃  今年应该为她办个特别的生日派对
Bob, she deserves a special party this year.
如果她日记里写的都是真的
If what it says in her diary is true,
那我得说她的确需要一个特别的派对
then I'd say she needs it.
非常需要
A lot.
说得对
It's true.
等等  你们都看过她的日记
Wait. You read her diary?
-是啊  -仅限不会让我吐的那部分
- Yeah. - What I can stomach.
我粗略地看了看  只想确保她没有嗑药
I just skim it to make sure she's not on drugs.
上面都说些什么
What... what does it say?
上面写着  "我没嗑药"
It says, "I'm not on drugs."
她过得很不好
It's pretty rough.
但她觉得今年会时来运转
But she thinks things will really turn around this year.
对  她还把今年称为"蒂娜之年"呢
Yeah, she dubbed it the "Year of Tina".
怎么每个人都看她日记
Why is everyone reading her diary?
写得不错啊
It's well-written.
她的文字比她本人丰满多了
She's better on the page than in person.
要是纳粹把我们抓走了
And what if the Nazis get us,
这就是我们全家唯一的乐子
and it's all we have of our family?
好吧  那就来办个最最特别的派对
Okay, fine. We'll make this birthday extra-special.
好
All right.
蒂娜  亲爱的  快过来
Tina, sweetie, come here.
怎么了
Yeah?
听好了  宝贝  我们想给你办一个
Listen, baby, we'd like you to have
最最特别的13岁生日派对
an extra-special 13th birthday party.
好好想一想
So take your time,
你想要什么来完美你的派对
and think about what would make "the perfect party".
我想办个男女混合派对
I'd like it to be a boy-girl party,
大家一起热闹热闹
with mingling.
我希望能闭店一天  把全班同学都请过来
I want to close the restaurant and invite my whole class over.
-不是吧  -我想请个DJ
- No. - And I want there to be a DJ,
我想跳舞  还想要台制烟机
and dancing, and a smoke machine,
派对开始两个小时后
and about two hours into the party,
要上演一出精彩桥段
I want there to be a moment
我要看着小吉米穿过人群向我走来
where I see Jimmy Jr. across the room,
我们慢慢拉近距离
and we're pulled toward each other.
我们在闪光球下对视
We meet under the disco ball,
然后接吻  直到我们的灵与肉合而为一
and we kiss until our bodies and souls become one.
老天
Oh, God.
那会是我的初吻
And it's my first kiss.
它将很完美  让我永生难忘
And it's perfect, and I remember it forever.
-怪胎  -好可怕
- Freak. -Scary.
你还真是费了不少心思
Wow. You've really put some thought into it.
听起来开销不小
That, uh, sounds expensive.
我只能办个
And I could do without
没有"和派丝多家小孩接吻"的派对
"the kissing Pesto's kid" part.
那算了  看来我注定无法拥有美好生活
Oh. It's okay, I guess I wasn't meant to have a good life.
鲍勃  借一步说话  给我过来
Bob, a word? Now?
-我不过  -过来
- Not now. - Now.
好吧
All right.
你想和小吉米・派丝多接吻吗
You want to kiss Jimmy Pesto Jr.?
想  很想  想了千万次
Yes. A lot. Many times.
我可以帮你  我来当你的接吻指导
I can help you. I'll be your kissing coordinator.
就算是我送你的生日礼物
It's my birthday present to you.
不用了  我想我知道怎么接吻
Yeah, I think I know how to kiss.
是吗  你以为你会接吻吗
Do you? You think you know how to kiss?
你知道怎么咬唇吗  你知道吗
You know how to lock lips, huh? Do you?
你自以为知道和男人接吻的感觉呢  蒂娜
You think you know what it feels like to kiss a man, Tina?!
如果你不知道自己在做什么
If you don't know what you're doing out there,
就很有可能送掉自己的小命  或者更惨
you could get yourself killed. Or worse!
性病  你听过吗  蒂娜
STDS, Tina, have you heard of them?
-疱疹你听过吗  听过吗  -听过
- Have you heard of herpes? Have you? - Yes.
-知道嘴上长疱疹什么感觉吗  -知道
- Do you know what herpes feels like on your mouth? - Yes.
什么  什么感觉的  说来听听
What? What is it? What?
就像嘴被割破了
Like, um, cuts on your mouth.
好像是那样的
That sounds right.
扇...  我还是扇吉恩吧
Sla... I'm gonna slap Gene.
闭店一天  弄台制烟机  还要整个DJ
Closing down the restaurant, getting a smoke machine, and a DJ?
这费用可不小
That's gonna add up.
我们这个月没有余钱了  琳
We have nothing extra this month, Lin.
但该做的我们还是得做啊
Well, we got to do what we got to do.
看看她
Look at her.
真可怜
She's so awkward.
她是个好女孩
She's a good girl.
好吧  我去和费舍奥德说说
Okay. I'll talk to Fischoeder
让他给我们宽限一下房租
about getting an extension on the rent.
雾好浓啊
It's foggy.
是  很浓
Yes, it is.
-你在吗  -我在
- Are you there? - I am.
为什么我们身处雾中
Why are we here in the fog?
我想见你
I-- I wanted to meet you,
然后你让我到这儿来见你
and then you told me to meet you here.
对了
Oh, that's right.
这是个不错的主意  我喜欢雾
It was a good idea. I love the fog.
费舍奥德先生
Listen, Mr. Fischoeder,
我知道我们谈过再也不拖欠房租的事
I know we talked about never doing this again,
可是  你能不能再宽限我们两周
but if you can just give us two extra weeks
这个月的房租
this month on the rent...
到此为止吧  鲍勃
I'm going to have to stop you right there, Bob.
你要接着说点别的吗
Were you-- were you going to follow that up with anything?
不要
No.
我好喜欢雾气在我披肩下浮动的感觉
Oh, I love the way the fog feels under my cape.
好吧  那我走了
Uh, right. I'll get going.
鲍勃  你看这样如何
Bob, listen. What do you think of this?
虽然我不会给你宽限房租
What if I don't give you an extension on your rent,
但我可以在我的众多副业中
but I do give you the opportunity
给你找一份兼职
to earn some extra money in one of my side businesses?
听起来还...  凑合
That sounds... sketchy.
凑合一下吧  鲍勃
Oh, it is, Bob.
不过  你得戴着这顶帽子
But you get to wear this hat.
那么  从下周开始
So, for the next week,
我就要去开出租了
I'll be driving a taxicab
挣钱给蒂娜开派对
to pay for Tina's party.
并且我会戴着这顶帽子
And I'll be wearing this hat.
-酷  -酷
- Cool! - Cool!
帽子酷还是工作酷
Cool hat or job?
-工作  -帽子  -谢谢你  老爸
- Job. - Hat. Thank you, dad.
这个派对会充满"咝咝"声
This party is gonna sizzle.
别这样
Stop it.
-鲍勃  鲍鲍  -怎么了
- Wait, wait. Bob, Bobby. - Yes?
你哪有时间开出租呢
When are you going to have time to drive a cab?
我白天在店里干活  琳
Well, I'll work the full day at the restaurant, Lin,
然后晚上开出租
then I'll go drive the cab
从晚上十点开到第二天早上六点
from 10:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m.
鲍勃
Aww, Bob.
好了  好了
All right, all right.
等等  你为什么非要戴帽子呢
Wait. Why do you have to wear a hat?
只是想让这份工作有点乐趣
Just let this be fun for me.
老爸  你不会失望的
Dad, you won't regret this.
当我在闪光球下亲吻小吉米时
When I kiss Jimmy Jr. under the disco ball,
就相当于我们都在闪光球下亲吻小吉米
it'll be like we're all kissing Jimmy Jr. under the disco ball.
我要先亲
I call first.
-是吗  -如果要亲他
- Really? - Well, if I'm gonna kiss him,
我可不想排在你们这些家伙的后面
I don't want to go after you guys.
我最后吧  我不讲究
I'll go last. I'm fine with that.
我们才不会亲小吉米呢
We're not kissing Jimmy Jr.
不  我们就会
Yes, we are!
十块口香糖进嘴  蒂娜
That's ten pieces of gum, Tina.
嚼啊  嚼啊
Chew! Chew!
接吻就好比用嘴打架
A kiss is like a fight with mouths.
时间到  吐出来
And... time. Spit.
我会毁了这个吻的
I'm going to destroy this kiss.
说这个为时尚早
Not yet.
这不是我的兼职老公嘛
There's my Johnny two-jobs.
为了梦幻生日派对拼命赚钱
Making money for the dream birthday party.
好了
Okay.
夜色已深  我要走了
Off into the night I go.
鲍鲍  注意安全
Bobby, be safe out there.
扯扯淡  小费会多些
And make chitchat. You'll get more tips.
别让计价器闲下来
Yeah, and keep the meter running.
小心嫖客
Watch out for pukers.
不要靠近一号公路
And stay away from Route One.
州际公路的支路全都前杠贴后杠的
It's bumper-to-bumper all the way to the interstate.
蒂娜  你怎么知道这些个
Tina, how did you know that?
我喜欢关注路况更新
I like traffic updates.
为什么
Why?
我喜欢听他们说  "前杠贴后杠"
I like when they say "bumper-to-bumper".
前杠贴后杠
"Bumper-to-bumper"?
好
Yeah.
我走了
Uh, bye.
这讨人厌的串珠座套
Stupid beaded seat cover.
好了
Ooh, okay.
上路吧
I get it.
听会儿广播  爽
FM. Nice.
知道吗  你是我的第一位客人
Hey, guess what? You're my first fare.
不是吧
Oh, no!
不要啊
No.
女士们  去哪啊
Uh, where to, ladies?
去"一刻钟与海洋"  乖乖
Fourth and Ocean, doll.
谢谢你载我们
Thanks for stopping.
多数司机都装正经  不肯载我们
Most cabbies are too prudish to pick us up.
那是...  因为...  你们...
And, uh, that's because you are...?
完美无瑕
Fabulous!
没错
That's true.
你们是挺无瑕的
Well... You're clearly fabulous.
是啊  是啊
Yeah. Yes.
注意前方  先生
Hey, eyes on the road, mister.
别盯着我们看啦
Yeah, stop staring at us.
我们又不是你的私人藏品
This ain't no library.
不要爱上我们哟  出租司机先生
Don't fall in love, Mr. Cabdriver.
你养不起我们的
You can't afford us.
到底是谁载谁啊
Hey, who's picking up who here?
小姐们  别往心里去  我只是开个玩笑
Hey. Don't worry, ladies. I'm kidding.
我有老婆
I'm, uh, I'm a married man.
我也有
So am I.
蒂娜  谁都可以用舌头把樱桃梗打成结
Now, Tina, anyone can tie a cherry stem with their tongue.
我们来看看你能把香蕉皮卷到什么程度
Let's see what you can do with this banana peel.
都含嘴里
Get it in there.
鲍鲍  早上好  你回来啦
Bobby! Good morning. You're home.
想不想知道昨晚异装癖妓者给谁上了一课
Yeah. Guess who learned a lot about transvestites last night.
我在那个网页上只停留了两秒钟
I was only on that web site for, like, two seconds.
啥  不  我指的是我自己
What? No. I was talking about me.
我拉了一群异装癖妓者
I picked up a group of transvestite hookers
他们让我见识了这座城市不为人知的另一面
who showed me a side of this town I never knew existed.
吉恩  罚你两天不许玩电脑
And, Gene, you're banned from the computer for two days.
看了那些东西之后  不玩也罢
After what I saw, I'm-I'm fine with that.
异装癖妓者是什么玩意
What's a transvestite hooker?
鲍勃  我认为早餐时间
Bob, I'm not sure
谈论这种话题很不适宜
this is appropriate breakfast conversation.
我想你说得对
I guess you're right.
或许我该去睡觉了
Maybe I should just try and go to sleep.
吉恩  宝贝  我想他睡着了
Gene, honey, I think he's sleeping.
可我要上学呢
I have to go to school.
别动地方
Shh, shh. Just hold still.
好恶心  这是口水还是汗水啊
Ew. Is this drool or sweat?
都有  你老爸睡觉时爱流汗淌口水
It's both. Your father is a very moist sleeper.
看我这两个宝贝男孩
Aw, look at my two boys.
漂亮
Nice.
蝴蝶结
Oh, a bow.
我去把它放到老爸头上
Let's put that on dad's head.
这是你的异性装头饰
There's your transvestite.
把相机拿来
Get the camera.
瓦格斯塔夫小学
这周六我要开生日派对
I'm having a birthday party this Saturday.
男女生均可参加
It's co-ed.
因为我就要成为女人了
Because I'm becoming a woman.
男女均可参加
Co-ed?
co-ed也有"女校荡妇"之意
我手心都湿了
My hands just got clammy.
小吉米
Hey, Jimmy Jr.
蒂娜
Hi, Tina.
这是我生日派对的邀请函
This is an invitation to my birthday party.
我发现你还没对我的邀请做出答复呢
Hey, I notice you haven't RSVP-ed to my party yet.
我得先问问我老爸同不同意
Um, I need to ask my dad for permission.
晚点告诉你好吗
Can I let you know later?
好的
Sure, okay.
屁股
Butt.
鲍勃  你还撑得住吗
Oh, how you holding up, Bob?
没事  我是说  有点累
Good. I mean, I'm tired.
我有可能拉了皮条
And, um, I might be a pimp.
你会需要一顶更大的帽子
You're gonna need a bigger hat.
好啦  你依然是年度模范父亲
Well, you're still father of the year.
蒂娜的派对将会非常精彩
Tina's party's gonna be amazing.
我买了闪光球和彩纸条
I got a disco ball and streamers.
派对现场会像白金汉宫一样
It's gonna be like Buckingham Palace.
英国王宫
是啊是啊
Yeah, yeah.
像54俱乐部
Studio 54.
上世纪七八十年代极受欢迎的迪斯科舞厅
你举了两个风马牛不相及的例子
Those are two very different examples.
你懂的  派对嘛
Well, you get the idea. You know. It's a party.
那  蒂娜开心吗
So, is Tina happy?
如果小吉米答复她的话  她会更开心
Uh, she'll be happier once Jimmy Jr. RSVPs.
她正在派丝多的店前  打探小吉米是否会来
She's over at Pesto's right now to see if he'll come.
我告诉她露露小蛮腰什么的
I told her to show some skin.
怎么样了
So, how'd it go?
小吉米不会来参加我的生日派对了
Jimmy Jr. isn't coming to my birthday party
虽然他本人很想来
even though he wants to,
因为他老爸不让他来
because his dad won't let him.
因为我们俩的爸爸是死对头
All because our dads hate each other.
对不起  蒂娜
Oh. Sorry, Tina.
我永远都不会知道
I'll never know
小吉米的双唇有多么柔软
how soft Jimmy Jr.'s lips are.
我猜它们应该非常柔软
My guess is, they're pretty soft,
就像...
like a...
就像小猫的肚子那样柔软
like a kitty cat's tummy.
吉恩  别说了
Gene, stop.
如果小吉米不来的话
Without Jimmy Jr.,
我就不想开派对了
I don't want to have a party.
我的大小姐  你老爸为了这个派对
Hey. Your father's been working very hard
可是拼了老命没日没夜地赚钱
for this party, young lady.
不想开也得开
It's going to happen.
是不是  鲍勃
Right, Bob?
我会重上一遍糖霜的  依旧很美味哦
I'll refrost it. It's still good.
真好吃呀
Mmm. Oh, it's delicious.
蒂娜宝贝  你老爸忙得脚打后脑勺
Tina, honey, your father's been working his you-know-what off,
开出租赚钱为你开派对呢
driving a cab to pay for this.
没错  我们还租下了制烟机
Yeah, and we've rented the smoke machine,
所以这个派对不开不行
so this party is definitely happening.
你忙得脚打后脑勺
You've been working your you-know-what off?
我还忙得脚打后菊花呢
I've been working my ass off!
夜以继日地训练她
Night and day training!
露易丝  别激动
Louise, take it easy.
你知道和她合作时  她是什么德行吗
Do you know what she was like when I started working with her?
她就是个令人作呕的笑柄  快看看她
She was a sick joke! Now look at her!
烟来喽
Incoming.
鲍勃  你去和吉米・派丝多讲讲理
Bob, you gotta go talk some sense into Jimmy Pesto.
这太不公平了
This isn't fair.
好吧
Fine.
吉米・派丝多
匹萨店
鲍勃
Uh, hey, Bob.
-你看起来像坨屎  -干得漂亮
- You look like crap. - Nice.
这个很搞笑
Yeah, that was funny.
吉米  我女儿蒂娜说
Look, Jimmy, my daughter Tina said
你禁止小吉米去参加她的生日派对
that Jimmy Jr. isn't allowed to go to her birthday party.
不管我们有什么矛盾都不应该影响孩子们
Whatever issues we have shouldn't matter.
请让小吉米参加派对吧
Just please let Jimmy Jr. Go.
好吧  好吧
Okay. Okay.
不过你知道  这要付出代价的  对吧
You know it's going to cost you, right?
天啊
Oh, God.
是啊  你看  鲍勃  我是个收藏家
Yeah, you see, Bob, I'm a collector
专门收藏稀有物品和异国情调纪念品
of rare and exotic trophies.
真是可悲
Well, that's pathetic.
而你拥有某样东西
And you have something
正好是我想收藏的
I want to add to my collection.
你的胡子
Your mustache.
你那浓密的  坚韧的
Your bushy, robust,
埋汰的  碍眼的胡子
filthy, eyesore of a moustache.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我希望你把胡子刮掉
I want you to shave your mustache,
装到袋里拿过来
and bring it over in a baggie,
然我会把它固定到墙上
and I'll pin it on the wall.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
-当作纪念品  -纪念品
- As a trophy. - Trophies.
我才不会把我的胡子给你
Well, I'm not giving you my mustache.
那我也不会把小吉米给你
Well, I'm not giving you Jimmy Jr. then.
你疯了吗  快让他去参加我女儿的派对
This is crazy, just let him go to my daughter's party.
既然你那么想要一袋毛发
If you want a bag of hair so bad,
为何不从你们店里的食物中挑些出来
why don't you just pick it out of the food you serve here?
中招了吧
Ka-boom!
你好大的胆子
How dare you.
你不给我胡子  我就不让小吉米去
No mustache, no bash.
他怎么说  宝贝
So, what'd he say, honey?
这对嘴唇还有上场的机会吗
Are these lips gonna see any playing time?
是啊  小吉米会来参加我的派对吗
Yeah, is Jimmy Jr. coming to my party?
不  蒂娜  抱歉  他来不了了
No, Tina. I'm sorry, he's not.
怎么了  你们俩没谈妥吗
What happened? You two couldn't work it out?
不  我们根本谈不到一起去  琳达
No! We couldn't work it out, Linda.
他说让小吉米参加派对的唯一方法就是
He said the only way he'll let Jimmy Jr. go
我把胡子刮下来给他
is if I shave my mustache and give it to him.
这么说小吉米还是有可能参加我的派对喽
So Jimmy Jr. can come to my party?
什么  不行  蒂娜
What? No, Tina.
你要做的就是刮掉胡子  然后他就来了
But if all you have to do is shave your mustache then he can come.
在我听来  你的意思就是小吉米能来
Yeah, it sounds to me like you just said that Jimmy Jr. can come.
我听到的也是这个意思  妥了
That's what I heard. Done deal.
我是不会把胡子刮掉的
I'm not shaving my mustache.
这是我的胡子
It's my mustache!
不行  小心点
Hey, no, watch it.
鲍鲍  要知道  就算你没有胡子
You know, Bobby, you're just as handsome
也还是一样帅  就是不太明显
without the mustache. Kind of.
我们做出的就是这种榜样吗  琳
Uh, so that's what we should show our kids, Lin--
和恐怖分子妥协  这样也可以吗
that it's okay to negotiate with terrorists?
为了我的孩子们  我宁愿这辈子都开夜车
I'd drive a cab every night for the rest of my life for my kids,
也绝不会让吉米・派丝多侮辱我
but I'm not letting Jimmy Pesto humiliate me.
你是天底下最自私的爸爸
You're the most selfish father in the world.
鲍勃
Oh, Bob.
晚安
Good night!
你不能把胡子刮了  鲍勃
You can't shave it, Bob.
你这样很迷人
It's glorious.
-我很怀念有胡子的日子  -怀念
- Oh, I miss having a mustache. - Pff. Miss it?
宝贝  我插一句  我从这儿都能看到它
Honey, news flash... I can see it from here.
你都能从外太空看到它
You can see it from space.
闭嘴吧  叉叉
Stop it, Cha-Cha.
我要把你眼球从脑袋瓜里按出来
I will thumb your eyeballs out of your skull.
好了好了
Hey, come on.
格丽特  你的...
Glitter, your...
你的上唇碰巧是我喜欢的类型
I happen to like the way your upper lip looks.
谢谢你  华伦王子
Thank you, Prince Valiant.
长篇冒险史诗漫画
《华伦王子》的主角
老爹  你该交班了吧
Your shift's almost over, right, Papi?
嗯...  差不多了
Yea... uh, yeah it is.
跟我们去喝一杯吧
Why don't you join us for a beer?
好啊  好啊
Yeah. Yeah.
去干几瓶酒  抽点大麻
We'll throw back a few beers and smoke some crack.
大麻
Crack?
那就只喝喝酒
Just the beer, then?
怎么回事
What is that?
-熏死我了  -我知道
- Ooh, your breath! - I know.
鲍鲍  听着
Bobby, listen.
我和蒂娜聊过了
All right, I talked to Tina,
我告诉她你一直在拼命工作
I told her how hard you've been working,
她同意参加今晚的派对了
and she agreed to come to the party tonight.
就一会儿  这已经很不错了
For a few minutes. It's something.
什么派对
What party?
鲍勃  你发什么神经
Bob, you're delirious.
-你才发神经  -你醉了
- Shh. You are. - You're drunk.
我也许抽了大麻  也许没抽
I may or may not have tried crack.
-好了  -就昨晚  我应该没抽
- Okay. - Last night. I don't think I did.
要真抽了的话  我很喜欢这感觉
But if I did, I liked it.
好了  鲍鲍  去眯一会
Okay, Bobby, listen, go take a nap,
我会看店的  去吧
and I'll watch the restaurant, please.
-把衣服脱了  -鲍鲍
- Take off your clothes. - Bobby!
-我得去睡会儿  -鲍鲍
- I got to go to bed. - Bobby?
-我不想这样做  -别闹了
- I don't want to do this. - Stop it.
别碰我  你这蠢货
Get your hands off me, sick idiot.
你个怪胎
Such a freak.
打起精神来
Pull it together.
我是能打到奥特曼的小怪兽
I'm like an animal!
小点声
Keep your voice down.
我是无敌大金刚
I'm like King Kong!
难以置信
Unbelievable.
-我得睡了  -晚安
- I need to go to bed. - Good night.
去把我的枕头拿来
Go get me special pillow.
快去  快去  快去
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
醒醒  小睡熊
Hey, sleepy bear.
几点了
What time is it?
离派对开始还有多久
How much longer till the party?
半小时前就开始了
It started a half hour ago.
什么
What? Ow! Oh.
你就让我这么一直睡着
You let me sleep all day?
怎么不把我叫醒啊
Why didn't you wake me up?
我试过了
I tried.
我都往你脸上削了多少片榨菜了
That was not the first pickle I dropped on your face.
男生不喜欢跳舞  女生又不肯向他们开口
The boys hate dancing, and the girls won't ask the boys.
外面死气沉沉的
It's a Mexican stalemate out there.
来啊  小伙子们  你们是花生酱
Come on, boys. You're the peanut butter.
姑娘们  你们是果冻
Girls, you're the jelly.
我们来做三明治吧
Let's make some sandwiches!
上帝啊  为什么莫特在变魔术
Oh, God, why is Mort doing magic?
那是他送给蒂娜的礼物
It's his gift to Tina.
露馅了  不对  变完了
Uh-oh. I mean, ta-da!
蒂娜  你看起来...  好美
Tina, you look... great.
我去给她打打气
Maybe I can cheer her up.
露易丝  给我喷雾
Louise, smoke me.
蒂娜  来和妈妈跳舞吧
Tina, dance with mommy.
这是可派对  放开点
It's a party. All right!
是不是有人开派对啊
Did someone say party?
他们不是我同学
They don't go to my school.
女士们  很抱歉
I'm sorry, ladies.
本店因举办私人派对  暂停营业
We're closed for a private party.
-鲍勃请我们来的  -鲍勃
- We were invited by Bob. - Bob?
你竟然邀请这些雌雄合体鸡
You invited transvestite prostitutes
来参加我们女儿的生日派对
to our daughter's birthday party?
不是  也许  我...
No. Maybe. I...
这个礼拜过得浑浑噩噩的
This week has been kind of a blur.
你们都来参加我女儿的生日派对吧
All of you are coming to my daughter's party.
我们会玩得快乐赛神仙
We're gonna have so much fun.
随便带些人来吧
And bring whoever you want.
我可能随口就答应了
I might have thrown it out there.
这里是甜蜜豆蔻派对吗
Is this the sweet 13 party?
爸  你叫来所有夜生活交的狐朋狗友
Dad, you brought all your nighttime friends,
却不愿剃掉胡子  为我请来小吉米吗
but you won't shave your mustache to get me Jimmy Jr.?
外套要放哪
Where do I put my coat?
你好啊  棉花糖糖
Oh, hey, marshmallow.
棉花糖糖  你的名字怎么来的
So, marshmallow, how'd you get your name?
如果给我一个甜薯派  我可以站在那上面
Cause if you show me a sweet potato pie, I am on top of it.
sweet patato pie是一种甜点
但也有"女性阴部"之意
我就知道
I knew it!
蒂娜  我知道你很失落
Tina, I know you're upset
因为小吉米没有来参加派对
because Jimmy Jr.'s not here,
而且这里的异装癖妓者
and that there are more transvestites
比你想象中要多  但是...
than you imagined, but...
除非你是小吉米  在这里亲吻我的双唇
Unless you're Jimmy Jr., and you're here to kiss my lips,
否则跟你说半句话我都嫌多
I don't want to talk to you.
别这样  小妹妹  这可是你的生日派对
Come on, girl. It's your party!
你也应该尽情享受嘛
You might as well enjoy it.
就像我常说的
It's like I always say,
天降苦难于你时
"When life gives you lemons...
你就对它竖中指
tuck them!"
我觉得我女友想表达的意思是
Uh, I think what my girlfriend here is trying to say is,
当你华丽绽放为女人的时机到来之时
when it's time for you to blossom into a woman,
任何事物都阻止不了你
you can't let anything stop you.
派对不能  男生不能
Not a party, not a boy,
即使所有医生都拒绝
and not a town full of doctors
为你切掉小鸡鸡的这座城市也不能
who refuse to remove your penis.
你有一个绝世好爸  宝贝
And you have a very good father, baby.
不要忘记这一点
Never forget that.
千真万确
It's true.
其他当爸的可不会像你爸这样
Not many fathers would make the sacrifices
牺牲自己  为你举办这场派对
your father made to throw you this party.
干两份活
Working two jobs.
他看见的事物  闻到的气味
The things he saw. The things he smelled.
他应该得到回报
He deserves an award.
鲍勃  你干了什么
Bob, what'd you do?
这下你的鼻子可不好过了
You lost your nose cozy.
鲍勃
Oh, Bob.
你把自己弄成个丑八怪来挽救蒂娜的派对
You made yourself ugly to save Tina's party.
是啊  琳达  所以我才不想把胡子剃了嘛
Yes, Linda, this is why I didn't want to do it.
但你知道  如果这样做能让蒂娜
But you know, it's worth it
欢快地度过她的豆蔻年华  就不白做
if it means Tina will be a happy teenager.
别盯着看了
Just stop staring.
快停下  不要剃
Stop! Don't do this.
我...  刚刚剃完
I... just did it.
你不必非得这样做
You don't need to.
我不想你这样
I don't want you to.
你知道胡子剃了还会再长的  对吧
You know how mustaches work, right?
别把它给吉米・派丝多
Well, don't give it to Jimmy Pesto.
那小吉米怎么办
What about Jimmy Jr.?
小吉米也不会使这个派对锦上添花
Jimmy Jr. isn't gonna make this party perfect.
-你已经让这个派对完美无比  -真的吗
- You already have. - Really?
很抱歉  对于你为我所做的一切
I'm sorry I didn't appreciate everything
之前我并没有心存感激
you've done for me.
我不是以女孩的身份感谢你
I didn't appreciate it as a girl,
而是以女人的身份感谢你
but I do appreciate it as a woman.
要是一分钟前听到你这话  我得乐死了
It would have been nice to hear you say that a minute ago.
你个禽兽
Bastard.
来享受派对吧  鲍勃
Come and join the party, Bob.
那个就是吉米・派丝多  叉叉
That's Jimmy Pesto, Cha-Cha.
我跟你提过的那个家伙
The guy I was telling you about.
等等  那个就是吉米・派丝多吗
Wait. That's Jimmy Pesto?!
我认识这个人
I know that guy.
我们都认识这个人
We all know that guy.
我们都知道他喜欢说"妈妈我要吃奶奶"
But we know him as baby num num.
"妈妈我要吃奶奶"
Baby num num?
等一下  你跟派丝多约过会
Wait. Pesto is one of your dates?
臭美吧他
He wishes.
我们在一个圈子混的
We run in the same circles.
他是"情欲地牢"的常客
He's a regular over at the desire dungeon.
大家都知道他是个"尿布情人"
He's what's known as a diaper-lover.
你知道那是什么意思吗
You know what that is?
臭气熏天
It's nasty.
吉米・派丝多是个尿布情人
Jimmy Pesto is a diaper-lover?
来啦  鲍勃
Hello, Bob.
看来我注定要赢得战利品了
Well, I see I'm getting my trophy after all.
"妈妈我要吃奶奶"
Bup, bup, bup, bup. Not so fast, baby num num.
"妈妈"...
Baby...
你怎么知道这个外号的
How do you know about that?
小宝贝儿
Hey, baby.
不
No.
我们只是想知道
We just wanted to see
牙签小宝贝儿
if wittle baby num num...
牙签:  讽刺他生殖器官短小
别说了  别声张
Shh. Come on. Quiet.
是否会改变主意
wanted to change his mind
让小吉米去参加蒂娜的生日派对
about letting Jimmy Jr. go to Tina's party.
还是  他想让整个"稀餐馆"都知道
Or maybe he wants the whole "Westaurant" to know about...
他有多么喜欢穿着纸尿布拉屎
how he likes to put on diapers and poop in them.
真不敢相信
I don't believe it.
谢谢你  老爸
Thanks, dad.
你是我遇到过的最棒的皮条客
You're the best pimp I'm ever gonna have.
我这辈子一直再等这句话  蒂娜
I've been waiting to hear those words all my life, Tina.
生日快乐
Happy birthday.
鲍鲍  过来帮我插蜡烛
Bobby, come help me with the candles.
这支曲子送给今天过生日的女孩
This one goes out to the birthday girl.
请原谅  过生日的女人
Pardon me. Birthday woman.
我很喜欢你这件衬衫
I like your shirt.
那些扣子可以扯开吗
Are those snaps?
可以  啪
Yes. Snap.
再扯一颗
One more.
啪
Snap.
想跳舞吗
Want to dance?
嗯
Yes.
上啊  蒂娜
It's go time, Tina.
让他的孩子都印上你的唇印
I want his kids to have hickeys.
我刚刚吻了我的初恋男友
I just kissed my first boy.
-我也是  -你个死鬼
- Me, too. - Oh, boo hoo.
快点把胡子蓄回来
Hurry up and grow that thing back.
我知道  难看死了
I know. It's bad.
好了  集中精神
Now! Concentrate!
应付一下
Push it out.
我在努力  琳
I'm trying, Lin.
用我的手指给你遮遮丑吧
Oh, let me cover it with my finger.
这样好多了
That's okay.
我要把这些胡茬粘在胸前
I'm gonna glue this to my chest
这样我就可以穿V字领的衣服了
so I can wear v-necks.
粘在你背后
Glue it to your back!
粘在你掌心
Oh, glue it to your palm.